bets2sport.com 2016-11-07

# Privacy & Policy

1\. Introduction

Thank you for visiting Bets2Sport.com, a site designed to inform, educate and entertain users regarding betting, all around the globe. This Privacy Policy focuses on to explain our visitors and users that how we use their information.

By accessing, using and/or downloading the site, you signify your consent to this privacy policy and signify your acceptance of our terms and conditions of services. If you do not agree to the entire terms of this policy, you should not access, download and/or use this site.

This site is primarily operated for providing fair and relevant information regarding betting and we serve as intermediary source and provide a mode to the user to connect with the various bookmakers but we do not claim to perform any betting activity or being involved in any of the gambling bustles.

2\. Personal Information we collect

As you may have thought, personal info is information that directly identifies you or allows us or others to contact you. While using the Site, you might be asked to give your name, e-mail address, username, and password. Personal details likewise may include details that could not be directly recognizable standing alone, however which may end up being directly recognizable when combined with personal details. Some pages as well as features on our Site can be utilized without giving any kind of personal information. For other pages, functionalities as well as services, you need to provide some personal details. Individual details are only collected from you if you wish to be the part of it.

3\. Non-Personal Information we collect

We may also collect some information about you that might be considered as non-personal. We may collect information regarding your preferences like odds, preferred bookmakers, or betting tools. It may include information about your computer, device and internet connection, IP address, browser, operating system, specific pages that you may prefer to access on the site or prior to or after visiting the site, the duration and time you spend on website and other general information about our visitors. Anyhow, this information cannot be used to identify you.

4\. Location Data

We may request access to or otherwise may receive information about your device location when you access the site. Your location data may be based on your IP address. We only use location data to improve user experience with the site.

Use of Information

We may freely use your non-personal information or aggregate information for any lawful purpose.

Our third party service providers and we may use Collected Information for:

__   Helping to administer the Site and the servers

__   Generating statistical information

__   Marketing, promoting or advertising the Site

__   Monitoring and analyzing Site traffic and usage patterns

__   Improving Site's content, including any online content and services that are available on the Site.

__   Registering and administrating your membership

__   Providing customer service and support

__   Considering your queries and concerns

__   Enforcing our Terms of Service and contracts with third parties

5\. Disclosure of your Information

Every authorization that you grant us in this Privacy Policy, you also grant to any third party that we may contract for the purpose of operating, upholding, renovating, or otherwise for improving the Site or its underlying files or systems. You agree not to hold us liable for the actions of any of these third parties, even if we would generally be held liable for their actions, and you must take legal action against them directly and they would commit any tort or other violated action against you.

6\. Cookies and Beacons

To recognize you when you return to the Site and to save your preferences, we use cookies. We also use **analytics cookies** to present data about user interaction with our Site, content and advertising campaigns, such as Site traffic. In addition, we use **advertising cookies** to manage, track, target and serve ads through our third-party service providers.

You may not be able to access the entire operation of the Site if cookies are disabled on your browser. Most web browsers are initially set to accept cookies. If you prefer, you can set your web browser to refuse cookies or to send alerts when cookies are sent to you. The "Help" feature on most browsers will assist you to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies and if you receive a new cookie then it will lend a hand for you to disable it.

7\. Our Third Party Service Providers

Advertising agencies, networks, and other companies may place advertisements on the Site, and on the Internet normally, and may use their own cookies, web beacons, and other technologies for gathering information regarding you. We do not control using such technology and bears no responsibility for the use of such technology to collect information of the visitors or users.

8\. Third Party Websites

We may link to the third party websites like bookmakers or betting sites from our Site. We have no control over, and are not accountable for these third party websites or their use of your personal information. This Privacy Policy does not apply to those websites or ads and we are not liable for the content found on those sites or the actions or privacy practices employed by any other website or app.

9\. Law Enforcements

We may disclose your information to a third party where we believe, in good faith that it is desirable to do so for the purposes of a civil action, criminal investigation, or other legal matter. We may also use and disclose information about you to establish or revise our legal rights, to declare and protect against legal claims, or if we believe such disclosure is necessary to investigate, prevent, or to take other actions regarding actual or suspected illegal or fraudulent activities or potential threats to the safety or well-being of any person.

10\. Security of Information

We make no guarantees for the security or privacy of your information. It is in our concern to keep the Site secure, and we take rational steps to protect our site against the unauthorized access, disclosure, misuse, alteration and destruction of the personal information under our control. We recommend that you use anti-virus software and other precautions to protect yourself from security threats. If you notice any breach of Site security, please notify us immediately.

11\. Changes to Privacy Policy

We may change or update this Privacy Policy from time to time and the older version will be replaced by the updated version.

12\. Age Barrier (Under 18)

As per company’s policies and norms, anyone who is under 18 is not liable for our site. For more details you must go through ([ 18+](http://www.bets2sport.com/help/age-barrier.php)).

13\. Contact

For any queries or feedbacks, please [contact us](http://www.bets2sport.com/contact-us.php)
